{
    "name": "C程序设计",
    "answers": [
        {
            "unit": "2.5.5",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "x+a%3*(int)(x+y)%2/4",
                    "answer": "2.500000"
                },
                {
                    "question": "+i*f-d/l",
                    "answer": "113.58"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "unit": "2.5.6",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "&",
                    "answer": "4"
                },
                {
                    "question": "|",
                    "answer": "119"
                },
                {
                    "question": "^",
                    "answer": "115"
                },
                {
                    "question": "^",
                    "answers": ["119", "115", "-9", "256", "1"]
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "unit": "2.5.7",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "假设a为整数变量",
                    "answer": "24"
                }
            ]
        }, {
            "unit": "2.5.8",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "sizeof",
                    "answer": "整型表达式"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "unit": "3.1",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "循环",
                    "answer": "可能一次都不执行"
                },
                {
                    "question": "3种",
                    "answer": "顺序"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "unit": "3.2",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "a=1,b=0",
                    "answer": "1,2"
                },
                {
                    "question": "k=11",
                    "answer": "11,13,b"
                },
                {
                    "question": "x=011",
                    "answer": "10"
                },
                {
                    "question": "a=2,b=5",
                    "answer": "a=%d,b=2"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "unit": "3.3",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "a;float",
                    "answer": "%d%f"
                },
                {
                    "question": "%d%d",
                    "answer": ","
                },
                {
                    "question": "a1、a2、",
                    "answer": "10A20B"
                },
                {
                    "question": "25和2.5",
                    "answer": "a=25,b=2.5"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "unit": "3.4",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "a、b、c、d",
                    "answer": "1、2、/\n、3"
                },
                {
                    "question": "12a345b789",
                    "answer": "2,345,1,a"
                },
                {
                    "question": "1＃22＃333",
                    "answer": "’1‘、’2‘、’3‘"
                },
                {
                    "question": "输入字符A",
                    "answer": "67 E"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}